커피
Coffee.
- 고마워
- 카푸치노
-Thank you.
-Cappuccino.
고마워
- 모니카는 뜨거운 사이다
- 고마워
And a nice, hot cider for Monica.
Thank you.
- 레이첼?
- 응?
Rach, why does my cinnamon stick
have an eraser?
왜 스틱에 지우개가 달렸지?
오... 왜냐고?
미안해
That's why.
Sorry.
The One With The Stoned Guy
챈들러?
Chandler?
테들락, 오늘 멋진데요
Miss Tedlock, you look lovely today.
소매 길이 만큼 아부해도
되는 거죠?
That is a very flattering
sleeve length on you.
코스틸릭 씨가 근무 마치고
사무실에 들르래요
Mr. Costilick would like you to stop
by his office today.
장난 메모 때문이라면
나랑은 아무 상관없어요
If it's about those prank memos,
I wasn't involved.
정말요, 믿어주세요
Nothing at all. Really.
그리고 말예요, 작업 환경도
이만하면 훌륭하다고 봐요
And frankly, those shenanigans have
no place in an office environment.
얘들아
Hey, you guys!
챈들러가 들어와서
놀라운 소식을 전할 거야
Chandler's coming and
he has incredible news.
그러니까 너희들은
챈들러가 오면...
So when he gets here,
let's all act, like, you know
- 안녕
됐어, 정말 재밌을 뻔했는데
Never mind. But it was gonna
be really good.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 별 일 없어?
What's going on?
그냥 평범한 하루였어
So it's a typical day at work...
숫자 입력하고 있는데 앨이
부르더니 프로세싱 감독을 하래
...and Big Al tells me he wants
to make me processing supervisor.
- 잘됐다
- 축하해
-That is great!
-Congratulations!
그래서... 관뒀어
So I quit.
왜?
Why?
왜냐구? 이건 일시적인
직업이었으니까
Why? This was a temp job.
챈들러, 너 거기 다닌 지
5년이나 됐어
Chandler, you've been there
for five years.
지금 승진하면 내가 하는 일을
인정하는 것밖에 안돼
I know, but if I took it, I'd be
admitting that this is what I do.
이제 휴지 가지러도
못 가겠네?
Does that mean we have to start buying
our own toilet paper?
'범인은 조이 트리비아니였다'
That was Joey Tribbiani
with the big picture. Dan?
월급도 오르겠네?
Was it more money?
상관없어
Doesn't matter. I just don't want
to be a guy who sits in his office...
밤늦게까지 사무실에 앉아서
위너스 걱정이나 하긴 싫어
...worrying about the WENUS.
위너스가 뭐야?
The "WENUS"?
컴퓨터 시스템을 이용했다는
뜻의 프로세싱 용어야
Weekly estimated net usage system.
It's a processing term.
아, 그 위너스
Oh, that WENUS.
그래서 어떡할 거야?
What will you do?
모르겠어, 그게 문제야
I don't know. But I won't
figure it out working there.
뭘 하고 싶은지는 모르겠고
그냥 관두고 싶었을 뿐이야
I have something you can do!
네가 할 만한 일이 있어
스티브라고, 새 고객이 있거든
I have this new massage client, Steve.
곧 레스토랑을 열 거라면서
주방장을 찾고 있더라
Anyway, he's opening up
a restaurant...
...and he's looking for a head chef.
피비?
-Hi, there.
-Hi.
너 요리사인 거 나도 알아
처음엔 널 생각했지만
I know. You're a chef
and I thought of you first.
지금 일자리가 필요한 건
챈들러잖아, 그러니까...
But Chandler's the one
who needs a job right now, so....
난 요리 경험이 많지가 않아
I just don't have a lot
of chef-ing experience.
토스트 레스토랑이라면 모를까
Unless it's an all-toast restaurant.
왜?
어떤 요리를 할 건데?
What is he looking for?
다양하게 하고 싶은가봐
모든 메뉴를 만들 사람을 찾아
He wants to do something eclectic.
He's looking for someone
who can create the entire menu.
세상에
그렇지?
어떻게 생각해?
So, what do you think?
고맙지만 나한테는 영
아닌 것 같아
Thanks. I just don't see myself
in a big, white hat.
좋아
모니카, 있잖아
Oh, Monica! Guess what?
a perfect run-up
and there he goes, a perfect....
이런 거 보면
인간이 진화한다는 것도
Watch stuff like this...
...and you realize
why evolution is just a theory.
이론에 불과한 것 같아
셔츠 사이로 젖꼭지 보여?
Can you see my nipples
through this shirt?
아니
No, but don't worry.
I'm sure they're still there.
걱정하지 마
안 보여도 달려있을 테니까
쫙 빼입고 어디 가는데?
Where are you going?
로버트 틸만이라고 직업 상담가
'샤샤삭'이랑 만나기로 했어
I have an appointment with Dr. Robert
Pilman, career counselor-a-go-go!
'샤샤삭'은 내가 그냥 붙인 거야
-I added the "a-go-go."
-Career counselor?
직업 상담가?
너희는 원하는 게 뭔지를
다 알잖아
You guys all know
what you want to do.
난 아냐
I don't.
소파에 앉아있는 너희들은
뭘 하고 싶은지를 알아
You guys in the living room
all know what you want to do.
목표가 있고 꿈이 있지
하지만 난 꿈이 없어
You have goals. You have dreams.
I don't have a dream!
꿈이 없다고 아예 내놓고
타령을 하는군
The lesser-known
"I Don't Have a Dream" speech.
살아있는 게 좋아
살아있는 게 좋아!
I love my life! I love my life!
'브라이언 송'이지!
"Brian's Song"!
그 사람 만난 일은 잘됐어?
-The meeting went great?
-So great!
잘됐어, 어디다 식당을
열지를 보여줬어
He showed me
where the restaurant's gonna be.
10가에 좋은 자리가 있는데
It's not too big or too small.
It's just right.
너무 크지도 않고
너무 작지도 않고 딱 좋아
금발 여자랑 곰 몇 마리가
장사하던 곳 아냐?
Was it formerly owned
by a blond woman and some bears?
오디션처럼 월요일 저녁에
식사를 대접하기로 했어
I'm cooking for him Monday,
kind of an audition.
피비, 너도 같이 오래
나한테도 잘된 일이야
Phoebe, he wants you here.
It's great. You can make yummy noises.
네가 냠냠 소리도 내주면
좋잖아
- 뭘 할 건데?
- 냠냠 소리 내라잖아
-What are you gonna make?
-Yummy noises.
모니카, 뭘 만들 거야?
-And Monica, what are you gonna make?
-I don't know. It's gotta be great.
나도 모르겠어
근사한 걸로 해야 되는데
I know what you can make!
I know!
뭘 만들면 좋을지 알아
그걸 만드는 거야
왜, 그걸 넣어서...
You should make that thing
with the stuff.
그거 알지?
그걸 넣어서 만드는 거야
You know that thing with the stuff?
나도 모르겠다
Okay, I don't know.
얘들아, 이 근처에서
데이트하기 좋은 곳 알아?
Anyone know a good date place
in the neighborhood?
토니스 어때?
스테이크 10인분 먹으면 공짜야
How about Tony's? If you finish
a 32-ounce steak, it's free.
알았어
사자랑 데이트하는 게 아니면
어디가 좋을까?
Anyone know a good place
if you're not dating a puma?
누구를 만나는데?
-Who are you going out with?
-ls this the bug lady?
곤충 아가씨?
사랑해, 로스
"I love you, Ross."
실리아는 곤충 아가씨가 아냐
곤충 박물관의 큐레이터지
Her name is Celia and
she's insect curator at the museum.
그래서, 뭐할 건데?
-What are you gonna do?
-Go out to dinner...
나가서 저녁을 먹고
다시 우리집으로 와서
원숭이 소개시켜주려고
...then bring her back to my place
and introduce her to my monkey.
저건 은유적인 표현이
아니란다
And he's not speaking metaphorically.
다시 집으로 온다고?
그럼... 그것도 하겠네?
So back to your place?
You thinking maybe....
글쎄, 나도 잘 모르겠지만
그랬으면 좋겠어
Well, I don't know....
I'm hoping....
그 원숭이 녀석
매력이 철철 넘치니까
That monkey is a chick magnet.
귀여운 털복숭이 얼굴만 보면
얘기는 끝나는 거야
She'll take one look at his cute,
little face and it'll seal the deal.
실리아, 괜찮아
아프게 하진 않을 거야
Celia, don't worry.
He's not gonna hurt you!
소리 좀 낮춰, 제발
Soothing tones.
미안해, 괜찮을 거야
자, 이거 먹어
-Here, Marcel.
-I can't stand this.
더 못 참아
발톱으로 내 머리를...
-He's got his claws on my
-Yeah, all right.
괜찮아, 그래
Okay, try this salmon mousse.
연어 무스 먹어봐
맛있다
Good.
아까 그 연어 무스보다 나아?
Is it better than
the other salmon mousse?
크림이 더 많은데
-It's creamier.
-Yeah? Well, is that better?
그래서, 더 맛있어?
모르겠어
생선에서 거품이 나오는 것 같아
I don't know.
We're talking about whipped fish.
조금 줄이는 게 좋겠어
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
맙소사, 무슨 일이야?
God, what happened to you?
8시간 반 동안 적성검사,
지능검사, 성격검사 받았는데
Eight and a half hours
of aptitude tests...
...intelligence tests, personality
tests, and what do I learn?
뭐라는 줄 알아?
다국적 대기업의 데이터
프로세싱 일이 내 적성이래
"You're suited for data processing for
a large multinational corporation."
잘됐네
지금 하고 있는 일이잖아
That's so great!
You already know how to do that.
말이 되니?
Can you believe it?
내가 겨우 그런 일이나
하면서 살아야겠어?
Don't I seem like I should
be doing something cool?
난 뭔가 중요한 일을 하는
사람이었으면 좋겠어
I just always pictured myself
doing something....
중요한 일을!
Something!
챈들러, 그 기분 알아
Chandler, I know, I know.
근데 있지, 이 셔츠 위로
네 젖꼭지 보인다
Hey, you can see your nipples
through this shirt.
좀 먹어봐
기운이 날 거야
Maybe this will cheer you up.
5시간 전에 포도 한 송이
먹었으니까 나랑 나눠 먹을래?
I had a grape about five hours ago,
so I better split this with you.
원래 작게 만드는 거야
전채 요리 전에 먹는 거거든
It's supposed to be small.
It's a pre-appetizer.
프랑스 식으로
어무즈 부쉬라는 거야
The French call it an amuse-bouche.
맛이 참 '어무즈'하다
Well, it is amusing.
여보세요
안녕, 웬디
Hi, Wendy. Yeah, 8:00.
그래, 8시야
뭐라고 했지?
시간당 10달러?
What did we say, $10 an hour?
좋아, 그래
Okay, great.
All right, I'll see you then.
그럼 그 때 봐, 안녕
뭐가 시간당 10달러야?
-$10 an hour for what?
-A waitress from work is helping me.
웨이트리스 일을
봐달라고 했어
웨이트리스?
Waitressing?
물론 널 먼저 생각했지
Of course I thought of you.
But....
근데...
-But....
-But, but....
근데 뭐?
일을 완벽하게 하고 싶었거든
But it's just this night
has to go just perfect, you know?
웬디는 전문 웨이트리스
이상이야
Wendy's more
of a professional waitress.
그래, 난 올림픽에 나가려고
아마추어로 남아있는 거야
And I'm maintaining my amateur status
so I can waitress in the Olympics.
거만떨고 싶진 않지만 나도
76년에 웨이터 한 적 있지
I don't mean to brag, but
I waited tables at lnnsbruck in '76.
꽤 잘나갔어
Took home a bronze.
먹을래?
Amuse-bouche?
말해봐
Talk to me.
좋아
오늘 아침 기차를 탔는데...
A weird thing happened
on the train this morning
아니, 아니, 그런 거 말고
야한 말을 해보라구
Talk dirty.
지금?
-Here?
-Come on. Come on.
그래
화끈한 말로 날 흥분시켜봐
Say something hot.
뭔데?
What? What?
뭐?
- 뭐?
- 음부
Vulva.
음부?
Vulva?
너무 당황했단 말야
I panicked, all right?
She took me by surprise.
얼마나 놀랐는데,
그래도 나쁘진 않았어
But it wasn't a total loss.
We ended up cuddling.
꼭 껴안고 잤거든
정말? 몇 번이나?
You cuddled? How many times?
닥쳐, 진짜 좋았어
Shut up. It was nice.
난 야한 얘기나 하는
그런 사람이 아니잖아
I don't think
I'm a dirty-talking kind of guy.
애인한테 어떻게 하고 싶은지
말하는 거야
Just say what you wanna do to her.
Or what you want her to do to you.
아님 애인이 너한테 해주길
바라는 거나
다른 사람이 무슨 짓을 할까
생각하는 거 있잖아
Or what other people
might be doing to each other.
그런 의미에서 나한테
한번 말해봐
I'll tell you what.
Try something on me.
농담이라고 말해줘
Please be kidding.
왜? 해봐
Why not?
눈을 감고
지금 뭘 하고 싶은지 말해봐
Just close your eyes and tell me
what you'd like to be doing right now.
좋아,
난 내 아파트에 있어
I'm in my apartment....
그리고?
-Yeah, what else?
-You're not there.
관둬, 난 내 집에 있고
넌 없어, 이런 거 그만하자
-We're not having this conversation.
-All right, I'll start. Ready?
좋아, 내가 시작할게
- 조이, 그만...
- 괜찮다니까, 준비됐지?
로스, 넌 날 흥분시켜
네 입술로 날 뜨겁게 달궈줘
Oh, Ross...
...you get me so hot.
I want your lips on me now.
이번엔 네 차례야
-Now you say something.
-I really don't think so.
싫은데
You like this woman, right?
You wanna see her again, right?
- 그 여자 좋아하잖아
- 그래
- 또 만나고 싶지?
나한테도 못하면서 그 여자한테
어떻게 야한 말을 하겠어?
If you can't talk dirty to me,
how will you talk dirty to her?
내 엉덩이를
어루만지고 싶다고 말해
Now tell me
you wanna caress my butt!
좋아, 돌아서
Okay, turn around.
내가 말할 때 쳐다보지 마
I don't want you staring at me.
좋아, 안 볼게
All right, I'm not looking.
Go ahead.
- 어서 말해
- 알았어
Okay.
좋아
I want
Okay, I want...
내 입술로... 네 뜨거운 몸을
느끼고 싶어
...to feel your hot, soft skin
with my lips.
잘한다
There you go.
IKeep going, keep going.
계속해, 계속
내...
내 달콤한 혀로...
I want to take my tongue and
혀로...
말해
Say it.
말해!
Say it!
네 온몸을 핥아...
run it all over your body...
널 흥분시켜서...
... until you're trembling with
계속해
With?
- 웃기고 싶다구
- 말해도 못 믿을 거야
-Funny story.
-You're not gonna believe this.
괜찮아, 둘이 붙어다닐 때부터
알아봤어
I was always rooting for you
two kids to get together.
- 그렇게만 하면 돼
- 시끄러
-The trembling thing was nice.
-Shut up!
챈들러, 너 자고 있을 때
옛날 직장에서 또 전화왔어
That guy from your old job
called again.
또?
- 또 오고 또 오고 또 왔어
- 또 왔지
-Again?
-And again and again and again.
여보세요?
또 왔다
And again.
15층 생활은 좀 어때요?
Hey, Mr. Costilick.
How's life on the 1 5th floor?
저도 생각나죠
Yeah, I miss you too.
사장님 댁에서 펜 훔치는
것보단 별로예요
It's a lot less satisfying
to steal pens from your own home.
그럼 고맙죠
That's very generous.
But this isn't about the money.
하지만 돈 때문이 아녜요
나한테는 단순한 직업보다는
정말 좋아하는 일이 필요해요
I need more than a job.
I need something I really care ab
아까 말씀하신 연말 보너스에
얹어주시는 건가요?
That's on top of the year-end bonus?
- 꿈을 생각해
- 꿈을 생각해야지
Your dream!
이봐요, 앨
지금 장난하는 겁니까?
Look, Al, I'm not
playing hardball here, okay?
협상하는 게 아녜요
거절하는 거라구요
This is not a negotiation.
This is a rejection!
그만, 숫자 말하지 말아요
숫자 좀 그만 말해요
Stop saying numbers!
사람 잘못 봤어요
사람 잘못 봤다구요
I'm telling you,
you've got the wrong guy!
그럼 월요일에 뵙죠
I'll see you Monday!
알아
사무실 엄청 크다
혼자 쓰는 방이라 그런가?
Wow! It's huge!
It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
완전 저택이네
This is a cube!
이것 봐라
Look at this.
창문도 있네
You have a window!
그래, 전망도 죽여
Yes, indeed-y.
With a beautiful view of
봐, 저 사람 오줌 눈다
Look! That guy's peeing!
전망은 그만 보고 이거 볼래?
That's enough of the view.
Check this out.
- 좋아, 앉아
- 그래
Okay, sit down here.
정말 끝내줘
This is great.
- 한다?
- 그래
-You ready?
-Yeah.
헬렌, 잠깐 들어올래요?
Helen, could you come in here?
고마워요, 그만 됐어요
Thank you, Helen. That'll be all.
이번이 마지막이에요
약속해요
Last time I do that.
I promise.
표정이 별로 안 좋다
-She doesn't seem very warm.
-I know. She has no personality.
별 개성이 없어서 그래
웬디, 이러지 마
Wendy, don't do this to me.
웬디, 얘기 끝난 거잖아
오기로 약속해놓고
We had a deal.
Yeah, you promised.
웬디, 웬디, 웬디
누구야?
-Who was that?
-Wendy bailed.
웬디가 약속을 어겼어
웨이트리스 해줄 사람이 없어
I have no waitress.
안됐구나
That's too bad.
Bye-bye.
나 간다
- 시간당 10달러
- 싫어
Ten dollars an hour!
Twelve dollars an hour!
12달러
나도 도와주고 싶지만
바람쐬고 오기로 결심했어
I wish I could, but I've made plans
to walk around.
너 결혼식장에서 도망쳤을 때
내가 도와줬잖아
When you ran out on your wedding,
I was there.
네 머리에 지붕을 씌워줬는데
아무 의미가 없단 말야?
I put a roof over your head!
If that means nothing....
시간당 20달러
Twenty dollars an hour.
좋아
Done.
모니카의 집에 오신 것을
환영합니다
Hello. Welcome to Monica's.
May I take your coat?
코트 주실래요?
- 안녕, 스티브
- 안녕, 모니카
-Hi, Steve.
-Hello, Monica.
안녕, 인사하는 아가씨
Hello, greeter girl.
- 레이첼이에요
- 그래
-This is Rachel.
-Yeah, okay.
맛있는 냄새가 난다
Everything smells so delicious.
이렇게 맛있는 냄새를
얼마 만에 맡는지 모르겠어
I can't remember ever smelling
such a delicious combination of
그래, 냄새가 난다구
Okay, smells.
집이 좋군
-It's a lovely apartment.
-Thank you. Would you like a tour?
고마워요
구경시켜 드릴까요?
그냥 인사 치레한 거야
I was just being polite,
but all right.
왜 저래?
택시를 타고 오는 길에
스티브가 한 대 피웠어
-What's up?
-ln the cab on the way over...
...Steve blazed up a doobie.
뭘?
What?
대마초 몰라?
기분 뿅 가는 거
Smoked a joint, you know?
Lit a bone. Weed, hemp, ganja
그래, 알았어
무슨 말인지 감 잡았어
I'm with you, Cheech.
괜찮을까?
-Do you think he's gonna be cool?
-ls it dry in here?
좀 건조하지 않아?
제가 와인 한 잔 드릴게요
Let me get you some wine.
첫 번째 코스를 대접할게요
I think we're ready
for our first course too.
이건 새우 라비올리
These are rock shrimp ravioli
in a cilantro ponzu sauce...
실란트로 폰주 소스예요
잘게 저민...
...with just a touch of minced...
생강이죠
...ginger.
어쩐지 엉덩이가
화끈거리더라
Well, smack my ass and call me Judy!
죽이는구만
-These are fantastic!
-Gosh! I'm so glad you liked them.
맛있다니 다행이네요
말이라고 해?
백 개라도 먹을 수 있어
Like them? I could eat 100 of them!
지금은 이게 전부예요
That's all there is of these...
8분 정도만 기다리시면
맛있는 양파 파이를 내놓을게요
...but in a few minutes,
we'll serve some tartlets.
파?
"Tartlets"?
파...
"Tartlets."
왜 이렇게 말이 새지?
Word has lost all meaning.
잠깐만요
제가 도와드릴까요?
Excuse me.
Can I help you with anything?
나도 뭘 찾는지 모르겠어
You know, I don't know
what I'm looking for.
죽인다, 타코 피군
Cool! Taco shells!
꼭 옥수수 같이 생겼지?
They're like a little
corn envelope, you know?
이거 드시면 입맛 버려요
-You don't wanna spoil your appetite.
-Hey, Sugar-O's!
신난다, '슈가 오'
안돼요
6분 정도만 기다리시면 돼요
You know, if you just wait
another 6 1 /2 minutes
마카로니와 치즈
우리 이거 만들어 먹어
Macaroni and cheese!
We gotta make this!
아뇨, 아니에요
-No, we don't.
-Oh, okay.
알았어, 그래, 미안
Sorry.
여기 좀 앉으세요
Why don't you just have a seat here?
좋아요
곰 과자 이리 줘요
-Give me the gummy bears.
-No.
싫어
이리 줘요
-Give them to me.
-We'll share.
- 나눠 먹자구
- 싫어요, 이리 줘요
그럼 안 줄 거야
-No. Give me the bears.
-You can't have any.
- 이리 줘요
- 싫어
It's not worth it!
곰이 쏟아졌다,
물에 빠졌어
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
서있지만 말고 911 불러
Don't just stand there.
Call 9-1 -1.
친구들, '슈가 오' 잡고
올라오게
Hey, fellas, grab onto a Sugar-O!
Save yourselves!
살려줘요, 물에 빠졌어요
살려줘요
Help! Help, I'm drowning!
살려줘요!
- 더 못 참아, 식사 끝났어요
- 뭐?
-That's it! Dinner is over!
-What! Why?
- 네?
- 왜?
왜냐구요?
만약에 내가 당신 집에 가서...
Why? What if I came into your office
and I started...?
예를 들 수가 없네요
I can't think of an example.
난 이 순간을 위해 7년을
기다렸는데
I've waited seven years
for an opportunity like this...
당신은 양파 파이 하나에
4분도 못 기다려요?
...and you can't wait 4 1 /2 minutes
for a tartlet?
아하!
그래서 미안하다고 했지
일을 할 수 없겠다고
So I told him,
"I'm sorry. That's how I feel."
그랬더니 내가 자기
엉덩이를 걷어찼다는 거야
And he told me I harsh-ed his buzz.
그렇게 먹지 말라고 말렸는데
자석을 씹어 먹잖아
Then I said, "Don't eat that.
It's a kitchen magnet."
내 말을 그렇게 안 듣더니
결국은 응급실로 실려갔어
And he didn't listen,
so we left him in the emergency room.
정말 안됐다
-Mon, I'm sorry.
-What a tool.
하필 자석을...
잘 한 거야
그런 사람 밑에서 일하지
않게 된 게 다행이야
-You did the right thing.
-You don't wanna work for that guy.
알아, 하지만 이번엔 정말
좋은 기회라고 생각했어
I just thought that this was it.
곧 좋아질 거야
넌 훌륭한 요리사니까
-Don't worry. You're an amazing chef.
-Those yummy noises? I wasn't faking.
내가 냠냠 소리 냈잖아
그거 가짜 아니었어
근데 돈 언제 줄 거야?
Am I gonna get paid
for the full three hours?
그냥 물어본 거야
나중에 얘기하자
Just a question.
We'll talk about it later.
실리아랑은 어떻게 됐어?
So, how did it go with Celia?
나 자신한테 놀랐지
-I was unbelievable.
-All right, Ross!
말해봐
저속한 말의 대가였어
I was the James Michener
of dirty talk.
듣도 보도 못한 얘기를
모조리 섭렵했지
It was the most elaborate filth
ever heard.
캐릭터, 이야기 구성,
I mean, there were characters,
plot lines, themes, a motif.
주제, 동기가 한 순간에
자리를 잡았지
At one point, there were villagers.
그래서?
And?
얘기를 너무 많이 했더니
둘 다 너무 피곤해서 그냥...
By the time we finished
all the dirty talk...
...it was late
and we were exhausted
- 껴안고 잤어?
- 정말 좋았다니까
-You cuddled.
-Yeah, which was nice.
우리 심야 영화 볼래?
Do you guys want to try to catch
a late movie?
챈들러를 기다려야 하지 않아?
-Shouldn't we wait for Chandler?
-Where the hell is he?
어디 있어?
프랜, 몇 신줄 나도 아는데
지금 위너스를 보고 있어
I know what time it is...
...but I'm looking at the WENUS
and I'm not happy!
뭐라고?
내 말 똑똑히 들어
Let me tell you something.
내가 신경쓰니까 프랜도
신경을 쓰라구, 알았어?
You will care about it because
I care about it. Got it? Good!
이런...
어때요?
How's this?
죄송해요
여긴 어때요?
Sorry. How about over here?
감각이 살아있단 뜻이에요
That means it's working.
- 아파요?
- 아뇨
-Does this hurt?
-No.
이건요?
How about this?
갑니다
There you go!
시원하다
I'm gonna throw up!